





## **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld.

# Summary

Jump to Section

Efficient professional with experience and proven knowledge of JavaScript,HTML CSS programming,growth hacking and social media management,aiming to leverage my skills to successfully fill the software developer role in a company

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects |

## **Work Experience**

Howzdat Edtech Pvt. Ltd. as Front End Developer Nov 2020 to Till Date

Working as a front-end Developer in a product based startup, Myjob is to design the UI and UX of the Company's product

Cloudstrats Technologies as Software Developer Intern Sep 2020 to Nov 2020

Software Developer intern, was working on different technologies on Microsoft Platforms like PowerApps and PowerBl. Developed Dynamic Covid Dashboard for different clients

GyanApp as Software Developer Intern Jul 2019 to Oct 2019

Did web crawling and scraping by parsing multiple pages using python libraries like Beautiful soup to create a database for the app and Managed Company's social media profiles ,modulated the content and used different social media platforms to increase the engagement on the company's app.

HPS Lab Designs Pvt. Ltd. as Customer Safety Consultant Jun 2017 to Nov 2017

startup focused on building solutions around automobile, human safety and internet of things.

^ Back to Top

### Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Sagar Institute of Research and Technology, Bhopal, in 2017

^ Back to Top

. . - . . . . . . . . .

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
JAVA,HTML5,CSS3,Javascript ES6,Jquery		0	0 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

^ Back to Top

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert	✓	✓	✓
Hindi	Expert	✓	✓	✓
Marathi	Expert	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

# **Projects**

Project Title: Cyber security quiz Client: self

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Nov 2020 - Nov 2020

Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: Created a quiz using HTML CSS and JS and was created to educate school kids about the threats over the internet

Project Title: My Blog: www.shrirangkundle.com

Client: Self

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: May 2020 - Till Date Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Project Details: Hosted an responsive blogging website using Wordpress and Elementor, Used Html, CSS to add several custom features on the website.

^ Back to Top

## **Affirmative Action**

## **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.